Hi, this is Liz Muller, from Liz's Hair Design, in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip, we're going to talk about how to grow African-American hair long.
We have a really beautiful model here.
This young lady actually was a marine, and her hair was in extensions for quite a long time.
What I did basically is when she came to me her hair was very thin in the top because of the extensions, and she had weak hair.
Her hair is fine, and she's got a relaxer in there, but she couldn't relax her hair for a while, so she basically needed a lot of treatments.
What I did for her is we constantly treated this hair once a week, and we put mask protein and moisture mask in this head of hair to treat it.
I also set the hair.
I believe in setting the hair because it just makes it strong, makes it really nice.
I don't believe in blowing it out.
I didn't want to pull the weak hair that's already been you know hurt and damaged from all the stuff she did.
So basically, setting the hair, treating it well, taking care of it, telling them to use certain products at home, like the Moroccan oil which is wonderful, or maybe you want them to use a semi di lino oil.
That's also very good for the hair.
Thank you.
This is Liz speaking.